startme.com 2016-04-16

# Privacy Policy - start.me

_Last updated: March 03, 2016_

**start.me BV** ("us", "we", or "our") operates the [start.me](https://start.me/) website (the "Service"). 

This page informs you of our policies regarding the collection, use and disclosure of Personal Information when you use our Service.

We will not use or share your information with anyone except as described in this Privacy Policy.

We use your Personal Information for providing and improving the Service. By using the Service, you agree to the collection and use of information in accordance with this policy. Unless otherwise defined in this Privacy Policy, terms used in this Privacy Policy have the same meanings as in our Terms and Conditions, accessible at [start.me/terms](https://start.me/terms). 

## Information Collection And Use

While using our Service, we may ask you to provide us with certain personally identifiable information that can be used to contact or identify you. Personally identifiable information may include, but is not limited to, your email address, name ("Personal Information").

## Log Data

We collect information that your browser sends whenever you visit our Service ("Log Data"). This Log Data may include information such as your computer's Internet Protocol ("IP") address, browser type, browser version, the pages of our Service that you visit, the time and date of your visit, the time spent on those pages and other statistics.

In addition, we may use third party services such as Google Analytics that collect, monitor and analyze this type of information in order to increase our Service's functionality. These third party service providers have their own privacy policies addressing how they use such information.

## Cookies

Cookies are files with small amount of data, which may include an anonymous unique identifier. Cookies are sent to your browser from a web site and stored on your computer's hard drive.

We use "cookies" to collect information. You can instruct your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, if you do not accept cookies, you may not be able to use some portions of our Service.

## Affiliate links

Our website contains affiliate marketing links, which means we get paid commission on sales of products or services purchased through these affiliate marketing links.

## DoubleClick Cookie

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on our Service. Google's use of the DoubleClick cookie enables it and its partners to serve ads to our users based on their visit to our Service or other web sites on the Internet.

You may opt out of the use of the DoubleClick Cookie for interest-based advertising by visiting the Google Ads Settings web page.

## Service Providers

We may employ third party companies and individuals to facilitate our Service, to provide the Service on our behalf, to perform Service-related services or to assist us in analyzing how our Service is used.

These third parties have access to your Personal Information only to perform these tasks on our behalf and are obligated not to disclose or use it for any other purpose.

## E-mail widget

If you use the e-mail widget to display your latest e-mails on your start.me page, additional privacy policies may apply.

#### Gmail

If you use a Gmail mailbox, you can check the Gmail privacy policy [here](https://www.gmail.com/intl/en_us/mail/help/terms.html). 

#### Context.io

We use the Context.IO e-mail API to power all other mailboxes (incl. Yahoo, Outlook, Yandex, etc). Context.IO anonymizes your e-mail content and uses it commercially to improve spam filters, detect and help stop phishing attacks, and help companies adopt best practices.

All your personal information (such as names, email addresses, and postal addresses) is removed. No part of the anonymized data can be traced to a specific email account.

  * **Privacy FAQ:** <https://context.io/privacy-faq>
  * **Opt-out:** [https://optout.context.io](https://optout.context.io/)

## Business Transaction

If start.me BV is involved in a merger, acquisition or asset sale, your Personal Information may be transferred. We will provide notice before your Personal Information is transferred and becomes subject to a different Privacy Policy.

## Security

The security of your Personal Information is important to us, but remember that no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage is 100% secure. While we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your Personal Information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.

## International Transfer

Your information, including Personal Information, may be transferred to — and maintained on — computers located outside of your state, province, country or other governmental jurisdiction where the data protection laws may differ than those from your jurisdiction.

If you are located outside Netherlands and choose to provide information to us, please note that we transfer the information, including Personal Information, to Netherlands and process it there.

Your consent to this Privacy Policy followed by your submission of such information represents your agreement to that transfer.

## Links To Other Sites

Our Service may contain links to other sites that are not operated by us. If you click on a third party link, you will be directed to that third party's site. We strongly advise you to review the Privacy Policy of every site you visit.

We have no control over, and assume no responsibility for the content, privacy policies or practices of any third party sites or services.

## Children's Privacy

Our Service does not address anyone under the age of 13 ("Children").

We do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under 13. If you are a parent or guardian and you are aware that your Children has provided us with Personal Information, please contact us. If we become aware that we have collected Personal Information from a children under age 13 without verification of parental consent, we take steps to remove that information from our servers.

## Changes To This Privacy Policy

We may update our Privacy Policy from time to time. We will notify you of any changes by posting the new Privacy Policy on this page.

You are advised to review this Privacy Policy periodically for any changes. Changes to this Privacy Policy are effective when they are posted on this page.

## Contact Us

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us at [privacy@start.me](mailto:privacy@start.me). 

start.me BV   
Waalsdorperweg 16   
2597 JB, The Hague   
The Netherlands
